Guide to the Church League of America Collection of the Research Files of Counterattack, the Wackenhut Corporation, and Karl Baarslag TAM.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Karl Baarslag Research Files, 1930-1968
  - John Birch Society, 1961-1964 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Black Liberation Front, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Book Find Club, 1945-1950 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Books - "How Conservative Books are Banned in Libraries" [Includes Reprint from American Legion Magazine], 1951-1961 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Branden Clemency Appeal, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Brainwashing [by Communists], 1952-1960 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Bricker Amendment, 1955-1957 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Broadview Research Corporation, Nov 1957 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1961-1965 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - California Free Enterprise Association, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Captive Nations Week, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation [Includes the Mindszenty Report], 1961-1964 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1955-1963 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Catholic Council on Civil Liberties, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Catholic Freedom Foundation [James W. Crockett], circa 1960 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Catholic Interracial Council - Interracial Review, 1958-1964 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Center for Research on Conflict Resolution, August 1962 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1961-1965 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1947-1964 (Box 42, Folder 23-24)
  - Chautauqua, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - China: Reasons for the Loss of [Articles on], 1951, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Christian Amendment Movement, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Christian Century, 1955-1961 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Christian Democratic Movement of Cuba [Full Page Ad in New York Times], Aug 26, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Christian Faith and Life Community (Laos House) [University of Texas], 1960 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1939-1961 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Christ's Mission (Christian Heritage), Jan 7, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - The Churchman [Protestant Episcopal Church Monthly Magazine], 1959-1962 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Church Peace Mission [Pacifist Group], 1950-1958 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Church Peace Union [John R. Inman - Council on Religion for International Peace], circa 1962 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties, 1961-1964 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Citizens Committee for Federal Aid for Public Schools, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Citizens Committee for International Development, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Citizens Councils, Feb 1960 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Citizens Defense Fund [John Goldmark Case], 1962 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Citizens for Freedom, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Citizens Foreign Relations Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Citizens United Press (Citizens United for America, Inc.), 1961 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Civic Research Bureau - State of Affairs, 1937-1939 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Civil Rights Congress, 1946, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Civil Rights Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Clergyman's Emergency Committee, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS), 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Columbia Council for the Gradualist Way to Peace, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Cold War Council (Los Angeles), 1962 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Commission on Freedom of the Press, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1961-1963 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Committee for a Review of Our China Policy, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Committee for Economic Development (CED), 1957-1963 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Committee for Fundamental American Freedoms, Inc., 1964 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Committee for International Growth, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Committee for Nonviolent Action, 1960-1963 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Committee for Peaceful Alternatives to the Atlantic Pact, Jan 1962 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Committee for Pillion Resolution, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Committee for Protection of Children from Nuclear Fallout, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Committee for Special Medical Aid to Cuba, April 1965 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Committee for Welfare, Education and Legal Defense (WELD), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Committee for World Development and World Disarmament, Oct 1959 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Committee of Arts, Letters, and Sciences for Kennedy for President [New York Times Endorsement, Annotated], Oct 1960 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - Committee of One Million Against the Admission of Communist China to the United Nations, 1958-1962 (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - Committee on Captive Nations, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - Committee on Electoral College Reform [American Good Government Society], 1963 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - Committee [Commission] on Government Security, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE) [AFL-CIO], 1959-1964 (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - Committee on Present Danger, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - Committee on University and World Affairs, Jan 1961 (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - Committee to Aid the Monroe Defendants [Monroe, North Carolina], Sep 1961 (Box 42, Folder 74)
  - Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 75)
  - Committee to Warn of the Arrival of Communist Merchandise on the Local Business Scene, 1962-1963 (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - Common Council for American Unity, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - Communism in Florida, 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - Communist Gift Organizations, Apr1965 (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - Communist Party Leaders Abroad, Dec 1964 (Box 42, Folder 80)
  - Communists: Legal Action Against [Justice Department], 1962 (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - Concern (Methodist Publication), 1962 (Box 42, Folder 82)
  - Concerned White Citizens of Alabama, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 83)
  - Conference for Legislation in the National Interest [in News and Views, Church League of America], July 1956 (Box 42, Folder 84)
  - Conference of Greater New York Peace Groups, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 85)
  - Conference on Economic Progress, Jan 1958 (Box 42, Folder 86)
  - Conference on Voting Restrictions in Southern States, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  - Congress of Conservatives, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 88)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) ["When We Tried to Give Labor to the Commies," American Mercury], Dec 1953 (Box 42, Folder 89)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1958-1964 (Box 42, Folder 90)
  - Conlon Associates (San Francisco) [Authors of Report on Asia], 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 91)
  - Conservative Alliance, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 92)
  - Constitution Party of Florida, Jun 1965 (Box 42, Folder 93)
  - Constitutional Amendments (Court of the Union), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 94)
  - Constitutional Conservative Movement in the United States [National Survey of Constitutional Conservatives], 1959 (Box 42, Folder 95)
  - Conservative Action, Inc. [California], 1964 (Box 42, Folder 96)
  - Consultative Conference on Desegregation, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 97)
  - Consumers Union of the United States, Inc. [Western Consumers Union, San Francisco], 1961 (Box 42, Folder 98)
  - Convicted Communists [Smith Act Cases], 1951-1958 (Box 42, Folder 99)
  - Council for Basic Education - Bulletin, Jan-May 1959 (Box 42, Folder 100)
  - Council on African Affairs [Madison Square Garden Rally, African National Congress], 1946, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 101)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1962-1964 (Box 42, Folder 102)
  - Council on World Affairs [World Affairs Councils], 1960-1963 (Box 42, Folder 103)
  - Critical Issues Council (of the Republican Citizens Committee), 1964 (Box 42, Folder 104)
  - Christian Rural Overseas Program (CROP) [Church World Service], 1964 (Box 42, Folder 105)
  - Eastern, Pennsylvania and Phillipsburg, New Jersey Investigation [Committee on Un-American Activities], 1954-1955 (Box 42, Folder 106)
  - Educational Programs - International, 1957, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 107)
  - Eisenhower Doctrine, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 108)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, 1955, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 109)
  - Eisenhower Statements, 1952, 1957-1963 (Box 42, Folder 110)
  - FACT (Magazine) [Barry Goldwater, America Psychiatric Association], 1964 (Box 42, Folder 111)
  - Federation of American Scientists, 1954, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 112)
  - "Fellow Traveler, The" [Article in New York Times Magazine], April 1949 (Box 42, Folder 113)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation [Pacifist Group], 1935-1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Fifth Amendment [Pleaders], 1951-1957 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Fifth Amendment Pleaders [List of Witnesses Before Senate Subcommittee to Plead Fifth Amendment], 1951-1956 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Florida's "Americanism vs. Communism" Course, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Florida Council on Human Relations, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Fluoridation, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Focus (Newsletter), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - "For America" [The Dan Smoot Report], 1957 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Forced Repatriation, 1955-1956 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Ford Foundation and Adjuncts, 1951-1964 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Aid - India, 1962-1963 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1960-1962 (Box 43, Folder 12-13)
  - Fort Monmouth Radar, 1953-1954, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Foundation for Religious Action in the Social and Civil Order (FRASCO), 1956-1964 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Foundations [and Relationship to Communism], 1955-1964 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Freedom Academy, 1961-1965 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Freedom Agenda Program [League of Women Voters], 1954-1956 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Freedom House, 1959-1965 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Free World Committee, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Friends of the First Amendment, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Friends (Society of) - Yearly Quaker Meetings, etc., 1963 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Friendship Book (San Francisco), 1953 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Front Organizations (Communist) [Profiles of], 1941-1956 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Fox Boston Post Series on Harvard (Communism at Harvard) [Baarslag-McCarthy Memoranda], 1953 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1955-1963 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Gaither Report, 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Gallup Poll - McCarthy Ratings, 1953-1962 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Genocide Treaty, 1950-1951 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Grass Roots League, Inc., 1953-1959 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Group Investigation Associates (Massachusetts) [in The Herald of Freedom and Metropolitan Review], 1965 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Group Research, Inc. [Index of the "Non-left"], 1963-1965 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Harvard University, 1951-1961 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Haryou-Act, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Hate Groups, 1953-1959 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Highlander Folk School, 1954-1965 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Hugh Moore Fund, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Humanity Guild, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Hungarian Uprising, 1956-circa 1962 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Iberica [Left and Anti-Franco Monthly Magazine], 1963 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Inclosure Number 76388 [from Department of Justice], 1952 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - The Independent (Formerly Expose), 1958-1963 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Independent Socialist Electoral Ticket, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1959-1963 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Defense Analysis (IDA), 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Institute for International Order [United Nations-Affiliated Organization], 1961-1963 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Institute on International Education, 1933, 1955-1959 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1951-1960 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Inter-American Association for Democracy and Freedom [Conference in Venezuela], 1960 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Interarmco, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Internal Security Act (of 1950), 1951-1955 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - International Labor Defense, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - International Labor Organization, 1954-1965 (Box 43, Folder 53-54)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, 1955-1960 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - International Union of Students, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science, 1949, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Koinonia Foundation, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Labor Youth League, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1961-1965 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - League of Women Voters, 1954-1965 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - Liberalism - General Definitions, etc., 1956-1961 (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - Liberation Committee for Africa [An Open Letter to President Kennedy], June 1961 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - Liberty Lobby, 1961-1964 (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Lifeline Foundation, Inc., undated (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - Little Rock, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Logan Act of 1799, 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Loyalty Oath, 1959-1965 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Mallory Decision [The Mallory Case], 1957-1960 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - The Marin Story, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Marzani and Munsell (Publishing Company), 1965 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Medical Aid to Cuba Committee, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Mental Health, 1954-1962 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Methodist Church - Manual on Christian Concerns, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Methodist Federation of Socialist Action, 1928-1965 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Milwaukee, WI - Ad Hoc Committee (Pro-Castro), 1961 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Minority of One, The [Monthly Newsletter], 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - The Nation, 1952-1965 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - National Alliance of Russian Solidarists (NTS), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - National Assembly for Democratic Rights, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - National Assembly of Social Workers, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1955-1965 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC) - Social Content Programs, etc., 1961 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - National Center for Education in Politics, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - National Citizens Commission for Public Schools, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - National Guardian, 1964-1965 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - National Indignation Convention, 1961-1963 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - National Information Bureau, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - National Institute of Social Relations, Inc. [Washington, D.C.], undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - National Lawyers Guild, 1953-1958 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - National Maritime Union, 1942-1960 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - National Municipal League, 1962-1963 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Negro National Labor Council [National Negro Labor Council], 1955 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - National Opinion Research Center, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - National Party of the United States of America, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - National Planning Association, 1957-1964 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - National Precinct Workers, Inc. (Chicago), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - National Renaissance Party [Neo-Nazi Group], 1963-1964 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - National Reprint Service, 1950-1955 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - National Right to Work Committee, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - National Security Council, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - National Service Board for Religious Objectors, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - National Service Corps, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1958-1961 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - National States Right Party (The Thunderbolt), 1962-1964 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - National Science Foundation, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - National Student Association, 1957-1965 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - National Student Committee for the Loyalty Oath, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - National Student Federation, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Nationwide Insurance (formerly Farm Bureau Insurance), 1955, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Negro American Labor Council, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Neighbors, Inc. [Nonprofit Organization in Washington, DC; Arts Festival], 1960-1964 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Nieman Foundation (Harvard), 1963 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - New England Party of Labor, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - New Leader, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - New World Review [Peabody Awards], 1957, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - New York Committee for the General Strike for Peace, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - New York Peace Information Center, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Newsweek, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Nonviolent Committee for Cuban Independence, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), 1956-1957 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Northern League, The, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Northern Student Movement, Nov 1964 (Box 44, Folder 59)
- Series IV: Research Files on California Student Movements, 1964-1969
  This series maintains original order. It is arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  This series contains research files collected by an undetermined creator regarding student movements and protests in California. Many of the files appear to have been collected to write a manuscript on events at the University of California, Berkeley. A draft of this untitled 1967 manuscript is included. Also present are clippings, typed summaries of news articles, fliers, posters, typed notes on radio and television broadcasts, internal reports, and index cards.
  The majority of the files document student activities at University of California, Berkeley and San Francisco State College. Subjects included in the files are student strikes, university building occupation, Vietnam War protests, sexual politics on campus, the Black Panthers and Black Power, the curriculum, Free Speech Movement, Students for a Democratic Society, and Community for New Politics. These files provide a right wing interpretation of student movements in the 1960s and also show the real or perceived links that the right wing tracked between the peace movement, student activism, the Communist Party USA, and other radical left wing groups.
  - John Birch Society (Important/Reported), 1965 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - College of San Mateo, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Hell's Angels (Important/Reported) and American Nazi Party, 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Presidio 27 Mutiny Trials, Jan-May 1969 (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - National Conference for New Politics, 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Oakland 7 Trial, Defense to Final Arguments (California Reports), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - People's Park, Berkeley, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - San Francisco State College, Reported, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 67-68)
  - San Francisco State College, Reported, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - San Francisco State College, Oct-Nov 1968 (Box 44, Folder 70-71)
  - San Francisco State College, Dec 1968 (Box 44, Folder 72-73)
  - San Francisco State College, Dec 1968-Jan 1969 (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - San Francisco State College, Jan 1969 (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - San Francisco State College, Jan 1969 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco State College (Recapitulation of Arrests), Jan 1969 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco State College, Feb 1969 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - San Jose State College, Dec 1968-Feb 1969 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, Material Used in Report, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 5-8)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, Material Not Used in Report, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, Used, Spec General, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - University of California, Berkeley, Free Speech Movement, Vietnam Day Conference, 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 12-14)
  - University of California B-I, Free Speech Movement, Before September, 1964-1966 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - University of California, Berkeley, Registered Student Organizations, 1964-1966 (Box 45, Folder 16-17)
  - University of California, Berkeley, Discarded Manuscript, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 18-20)
  - University of California, Berkeley, Cleaver and Grape Issues, Sep-Nov 1968 (Box 45, Folder 21-23)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 9th Report, No. II, Late 1968-Jan 1969 (Box 45, Folder 24-25)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 9th Report, No. II, Feb 1969 (Box 45, Folder 26-27)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 9th Report, No. II, Mar-Apr 1969 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - October 1966, Oct 1966 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - November 1966, Nov 1966 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - War on Poverty, Oakland Economic Development Council, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - December 1966, No. 1 (Box 45, Folder 32-33)
  - December 1966, No. 2, Dec 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - January 1967, No. 1, Thru Kerr Firing, Jan 1967 (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
  - January 1967, No. 2, Jan 1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - February 1967, No. 1, Feb 1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - February 1967, No. 2, Feb 1967 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - March 1967, Leaflets and Clippings, Mar 1967 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - April 1967, No. 1, Apr 1967 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - April 1967, No. 2, Apr 1967 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - May 1967, No. 1 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - May 1967, No. 2 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - June 1967, No. 1, Jun 1967 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - July 1967 (Only 1), Jul 1967 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - August 1967, No. 1, Aug 1967 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - August 1967, No. 2, Aug 1967 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - September 1967, No. 1, Sep 1967 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - October 1967-See Stop the Draft Riots, Oct 1967 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Stop the Draft Walk, October 16-21, Report: November 15-19, 1967, Dec 1966-Oct 1967 (Box 46, Folder 18-19)
  - November 1967 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - December 1967 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - January 1968, Jan 1968 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - February 1968 [Associated Students of the University of California, Black Power in Schools], Feb 1968 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - March 1968, Mar 1968 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - April-May 1968, Apr-May 1968 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - June, July, and August 1968, Jun-Aug 1968 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - September 1968, Sep 1968 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - October 1968 (See also University of California, Berkeley-Cleaver and Students for a Democratic Society and San Francisco State College), Oct 1968 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - November 1968 (See Also Students for a Democratic Society, and University of California, Berkeley), Nov 1968 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - December 1968 (See also San Francisco State), Dec 1968 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - January 1969, Jan 1969 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - February 1969, Feb 1969 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - March 1969, Mar 1969 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - April 1969, Apr 1969 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - May and June 1969, May-Jun 1969 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - June 1969, Jun 1969 (Box 47, Folder 7)